ILGWU Political/Legislative Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/142
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Committee on Political Education, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Congressional Black Caucus Foundation's 22nd Annual Legislative Weekend, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  September 23-27
- Congress - General, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Child Care/Child Labor, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO News, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO News, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Abrams Campaign, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Betty Davis - Calender and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Clinton/Gore Material, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Clinton Campaign Buttons, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Clinton/Gore Torchlight Parade and Rally, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Clinton for President Campaign Material, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Clinton Statements and Articles, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- President Bush's Veto Record, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- The Outrageous Adventures of George and Dan, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- NAFTA, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Expenses, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Health Care, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Union Label Department, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- GATT, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Committee of Correspondence Returned Mail, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Legislative Alert Listings by District, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Betty Davis Schedule, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO News, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO News, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Child Labor Coalition, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Congress - General, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Haiti, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Resumes (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Receipts and Invoices, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Committees of Correspondence, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Legislative Alert Listings by District, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Committee of Correspondence Returned Mail, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Health Care, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Justice, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO News, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Proposal for City Originals, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- City Council Candidates, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- "C" General, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Democratic National Committee, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- United Nations World Women's Conference, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- National Knitwear and Sportswear Association, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- OSHA Reform, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Citizen Action, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Northeast, Western Pennsylvania, and Ohio Department, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Letters to Congress, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Legislative Reports, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Correspondence with Congressmen, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Finance Department and Expenses, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- 1199 News, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- White House Weekly, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  December 5
- Consumer Education Program from American Express Company, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  Fall
- Veteran's Voice, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  Volume 8, Number 2
- People for the American Way, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  Volume 1, Number 1
- Elder Law Forum, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  Volume 6, Number 2
- CDF Reports, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- The Italian-American Labor Council News, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  Volume 6, Number 3
- Vital Signs: News from the National Black Women's Health Project, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  Number 1
- Utility Workers' Light, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  July
- New York Teacher, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Mail Receipts, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- United States Senate, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Challenge, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  September-October
- "The Vote on the Uruguay Round Should Not Be Rushed", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Fuel Expenses, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Memorandum on Endorsed Candidates for the Primaries, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- New York, Ohio, and Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Health Care, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Lobbyists, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- GATT, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Notes From Emily: A Political Network for Democratic Women, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  January
- 1199 News, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  Volume 12, Numbers 1-2
- Election Night Score Card, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- New York Times Articles - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- New York Times Articles - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Immigration Articles, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- New York Times Articles - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- NAACP Articles, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- New York Times Articles - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- New York Times Articles - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- New York Times Articles - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Calendars, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Calendars, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Calendars, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Calendars, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Contributions by State, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Contributions by State, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Contributions by State, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Contributions by State, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Federal Election Commission, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Evelyn Dubrow Calendar and Schedule, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Garment Center Rally Expenses, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Federal Election Commission, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- New York State Assembly, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO News, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO News, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO General, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Congress - Articles and Thank You Letters, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Basin Electric Power Cooperative Report, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Cope and AFL-CIO IUD, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Legislative Alert Listing, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO News, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Consumer Federation of America and Consumer Assembly, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO News, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Democrats - Articles and Newsletters, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Cope Committee on Political Education, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Meetings and Memorandums for Evelyn Dubrow, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Fiber, Fabric, and Apparel Coalition for Trade (FFACT), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Cesar Chavez, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Receipts and Invoices, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Jewish Labor Committee Biennial Convention, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  June 3-5
- Justice, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Jay Mazur Correspondence, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Jay Mazur Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Jay Mazur Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Dukakis, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- The State of Working America, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- American Family Celebration, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Gus Tyler Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Campaign Committee Fund, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- National Democratic Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- New York Times - Miscellaneous Articles, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- New York Times - Miscellaneous Articles, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- RWDSU Record, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Local 89-22-1 News, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Volume 4, Number 1
- Local 99 News, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Volume 30, Number 4-5
- Knitgoods Workers' Union Voice, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  Volume 50, Number 2
- Independent Action News, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  Volume 5, Number 1
- The O'Leary/Kamber Report, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Volume 3, Issue 1
- Insider's Briefing, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  1st Quarter
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Presidential Campaign Material, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Federal Express Post Office, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Focus Newsletter, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Volume 1, Number 5
- Telephone Voter Registration Campaign, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Project Vote, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Senate - Correspondence and Articles, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Model Garment Program, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Apparel, Textile, and Shoe Imports, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- New York City Voter Registration Information, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Americans for Energy Independence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO News, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO News, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO News, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Schedule and Calendar, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Calendar and Schedule, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Calendar and Schedule, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- ACTWU, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO IUD General, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Day Care - H.R. 541, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- CLUW Women Activity, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Congress - General, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Congressional Black Caucus Foundation, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Evelyn Dubrow - General, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Barbara Warden and Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Francis X. Gannon and Associates (Film), 1986 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- G.E.B. Committee for Retiree Services, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- General Advisory Council, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- H. Res. 172, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Health, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Homework, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Personal Contributions - David Wells, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Imports, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Inter-Office, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Justice, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- "N" General, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Correspondence to Jay Mazur, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Memos from Gus Tyler, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Memos from Jay Mazur, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Memos from Jay Mazur, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Memos from David Wells, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Minimum Wage H.R. 4493, Mario Biaggi, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- NAACP, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- National Committee on Pay Equity, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- National Democratic Club, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- The National Urban Coalition, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- National Urban League, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- New York Congressional Tour, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Newspapers and Issues - Other Locals, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- National Organization for Women (N.O.W.), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- New York State Festival, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Senate 777 - Guaranteed Job Opportunity Program (GJOP), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- IlGWU Finance Department, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Senator Terry Sanford - Sanford Steering Committee on Finance, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Senate - General, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Beverly Shulman, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Southeast (Bonanno), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Solutions for the New Workforce: A National Conference on Policy Options, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  September 28-29
- Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC), 1986 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- State Issues Forum, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Taxes, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Testimonies, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- The Trade and International Economic Policy Reform Act, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Trade Articles, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- National Center for Policy Alternatives - State Issues Forum, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- U.S. Senate Democratic Leadership Circle, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Facts on Women Workers, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Washington Alert Newsline, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- National Women's Political Caucus Biennial Convention, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Women's National Democratic Club, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Weal Washington Report, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Center on Budget and Policy Priorities, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Democratic National Committee, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Delegate Selection for the 1992 Convention (Box 22, Folder 10)
- CLUW, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Fashion Forward, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  Volume 1, Number 1-2
- "The Union's Call for Cooperation" by Jay Mazur, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Civil Rights, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Congress - General, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Child Care, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- 1991 News (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Letters to Evelyn Dubrow, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- U.S.-Mexico Free Trade Agreement, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Martin Luther King Jr Federal Holiday Commission, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- National Rainbow Coalition, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Letters to Jay Mazur, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- "M" General, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Citizens Fund, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- NAFTA Rules of Origin, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- National Women's Law Center, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- OSHA Reform, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO IUD, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Inter-Office Memos, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- La Mujer Obrera, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Justice, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Justice Memos, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Articles - Politics, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Payroll Change Advice, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- The Winning Slate, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO News, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO News, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Rally - General, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Rally - General, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- TV Broadcasts, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Anita Hill Articles, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Senate Candidates, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Workplace Fairness Act, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- RDWSU Record, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Local 89-22-1, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  Volume 6, Numbers 2-4
- Governor Ann Richards' New Texas News, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Volume 1, Numbers 1-2
- Kentucky Journal Politics and Issues, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Pipeline, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  Issue 22
- Demogram, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  Volume 11, Number 2
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Labor and Investments, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Forum for the First, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Newsletters - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Just Peace, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- New York City Congressional Tour, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Margo Pave, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Post Office Express Receipts, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Retiree Services, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Brooklyn Political Representatives (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Calendar, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Health Care, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Ann W. Richards, Texas, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Democratic Governors' Association, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Trade, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Health Care and Workplace Fairness, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Health Care Meeting, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  September 3
- Evelyn Dubrow - Expenses and Invitations, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Invitations to Dinners and Special Events, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- National Education Director's Conference, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Evelyn Dubrow Scholarship, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Thank You Letters, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Trade Bills, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO News, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO News, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- General Expenses, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Bills and Invoices, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women Membership List, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Beverly Shulman - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women - General, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Congress - General, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Health Insurance, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Constitution, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Finance Department - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- General Advisory Council (GAC) Conference, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- NAFTA, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Briefing Book for the 103rd Congress (GATT/NAFTA), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- NAFTA, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Caribbean American Community Comprehensive Center - Trade and Culture Expo, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- NAFTA, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NAFTA, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NAFTA, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- House Vote on NAFTA, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Inaugural Events Schedule, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Inter-Office Memos, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Gephardt Breakfast, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  December 2
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Robert Reich, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Jobs with Justice, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Justice, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- The Legislative Gazette, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Phone, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Luncheon and Dinner Invitations, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Leslie Fay, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Children's Health, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Health Care, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Health Care Task Force, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Jobs with Justice Lobby Reports, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- New York City Chapter, Coalition of Labor Union Women Luncheon, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  November 7
- Health Care, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Balanced Budget Amendment, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Board of Elections, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Citizens Trade Campaign Contact List, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Dinkins and Giuliani, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Mildred Holder Case Study, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- RWDSU Record, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Roll Call, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Utility Workers' Light, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- 1199 News, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Dinkins and Giuliani, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Phone Bank, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Clinton Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Receipts, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- New Jersey Council of ILGWU Retirees, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- 103rd Congress, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Evelyn Dubrow Scholarship, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- The Sophie Davis School of Biomedical Education, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Senate - General, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- NAFTA, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Rallies, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Trade - General, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Mayoral Campaign, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- NAFTA and Immigration, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- NAFTA and Immigration, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- NAFTA and Immigration, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- NAFTA and Immigration, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Summer Stage, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Calendar, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Articles and Letters, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Appointment Book, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Locals, Joint Boards, District Councils Area Offices and Affiliated Organizations, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Cope Administration and Operating Committee, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- "They Represent You" Pamphlet, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Correspondence with Evelyn Dubrow, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- 103rd Congress United States House of Representatives, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Congress - General, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Let's Get Moving: Organizing for the '90s, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- School Readiness Act, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Education Directors, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Memo Letterheads (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Richard Gephardt Breakfast, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  September 24
- Agreement Between Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 153 and Separate Participating Offices of ILGWU, 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- ILGWU State and Local Election Fund, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- City Council, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Congratulation Letters, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Congressmen - General, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)